[
    {
        "number": 1,
        "tagSid": "xD4AdwnwTKG",
        "prompt": "What is a job hazard analysis?",
        "answer": 1,
        "source": "Participant Manual Page 11",
        "options": [
            "A tallying of all the hazards found on the job",
            "A technique that focuses on job tasks as a way to identify and correct hazards",
            "A technique for analyzing job hazards and assigning them to appropriate categories",
            "A technique for evaluating employees on the job to make sure they are working"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 2,
        "tagSid": "e6Nkfzwwrb2",
        "prompt": "When considering controls that protect a worker from on-the-job hazards, which type of control is the most important?",
        "answer": 0,
        "source": "Participant Manual Page 12",
        "options": [
            "Engineering controls",
            "Administrative controls",
            "Training controls",
            "Personal protective equipment"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 3,
        "tagSid": "VlrLkW9suxt",
        "prompt": "Employees who work on scaffolds must be protected from falling if the level of the scaffold is feet above the level below it.",
        "answer": 1,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.451(g)(1)",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            15,
            250
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 4,
        "tagSid": "GRhk003LaF7",
        "prompt": "In a personal fall arrest system, lanyards and vertical lifelines must have a minimum  breaking strength of:",
        "answer": 2,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.502(d)(9)",
        "options": [
            "2,000 pounds",
            "3,500 pounds",
            "5,000 pounds",
            "6,500 pounds"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 5,
        "tagSid": "rIriFrvmID5",
        "prompt": "Personal fall arrest systems, when stopping a fall, must be rigged so that no employee can free fall more than feet, nor contact any lower level.",
        "answer": 0,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.502(d)(16)(iii)",
        "options": [
            6,
            8,
            10,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 6,
        "tagSid": "Ia903uWSpnO",
        "prompt": "When fall arrest equipment is used, employers must assure that:",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA29CFR 1926.502(d)(16)",
        "options": [
            "Users have calculated total fall distance.",
            "All equipment is properly inspected before each use.",
            "A rescue plan is in place to rescue a fallen employee.",
            "All of the above."
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 7,
        "tagSid": "kfVNrdvbjDv",
        "prompt": "When is it necessary to use lockout/tagout procedures to prevent electrical injuries?",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1910.147(a)(1)(i)",
        "options": [
            "When anyone is working around electrical equipment",
            "When anyone is working on equipment that has multiple energy sources",
            "When two or more employees are performing maintenance on the same electrical equipment",
            "When there is potential for an unexpected energization of equipment that could  cause injury to an employee"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 8,
        "tagSid": "6rqihQktVg4",
        "prompt": "Ground Fault Circuit Interrupters (GFCI) are required by the National Electrical Code:",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.404(b)(1)",
        "options": [
            "When there are wet conditions.",
            "On all temporary power circuits.",
            "On portable generators over 5,000 watts.",
            "All of the above."
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 9,
        "tagSid": "dD0ffvhNJ0F",
        "prompt": "Who should be given access to electrical installations that are locked in a vault, room,  closet or fenced area?",
        "answer": 1,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.403(j)(2)",
        "options": [
            "A supervisor only",
            "A qualified person only",
            "Anyone with a legitimate reason for entering",
            "Anyone who needs to work on the installation"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 10,
        "tagSid": "2suVezoL8OR",
        "prompt": "When may guards be removed from powered equipment?",
        "answer": 2,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1910.147(a)(2)(ii)(A)",
        "options": [
            "When proper PPE is used",
            "When something is stuck in it",
            "When the equipment is off and locked out",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 11,
        "tagSid": "5Z1JRVInRZY",
        "prompt": "Equipment such as cranes, forklifts, backhoes and scaffolding must maintain  at least a __________ foot minimum clearance from overhead power lines.",
        "answer": 1,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.600(a)(6)",
        "options": [
            6,
            10,
            12,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 12,
        "tagSid": "7dIGEf8ET0M",
        "prompt": "A stairway, ladder, ramp or other safe means of egress must be located in trench excavations that are or more in depth.",
        "answer": 2,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.651(c)(2)",
        "options": [
            "2 feet",
            "3 feet",
            "4 feet",
            "5 feet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 13,
        "tagSid": "bQP0gAOyjpG",
        "prompt": "How far back from an excavation must the spoils be?",
        "answer": 0,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.651(j)(2)",
        "options": [
            "2 feet",
            "6 feet",
            "10 feet",
            "12 feet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 14,
        "tagSid": "eJnWR72FY9Z",
        "prompt": "Excavations over 6 feet deep and not obviously visible must be, at minimum:",
        "answer": 0,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.501(b)(7)(i)",
        "options": [
            "Barricaded or marked.",
            "Protected by guardrails.",
            "Covered with traffic plates.",
            "No protection is required."
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 15,
        "tagSid": "umU0exIZt04",
        "prompt": "How often should vehicles being used at worksites be inspected?",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.601(b)(14)",
        "options": [
            "Annually",
            "Monthly",
            "Weekly",
            "Daily, at the beginning of each shift"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 16,
        "tagSid": "oD8pOG88PH1",
        "prompt": "To prevent worker run-over accidents, which of the following should be used?",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.602(a)(9)",
        "options": [
            "Back-up alarms",
            "Spotters for equipment",
            "High visibility clothing",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 17,
        "tagSid": "mBMW94eUOMg",
        "prompt": "Employees who direct or signal crane movements must be:",
        "answer": 1,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.1428",
        "options": [
            "Certified.",
            "Qualified by testing.",
            "Wearing a colored vest.",
            "Able to also operate the crane."
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 18,
        "tagSid": "IKqsoK4h4zC",
        "prompt": "Employees working from articulating boom lifts must:",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA 29CFR 1926.453",
        "options": [
            "Be tied off to the lift.",
            "Be trained to operate the lift.",
            "Keep their feet on the floor of the lift.",
            "All of the above."
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 19,
        "tagSid": "ddBDFkSnqI3",
        "prompt": "Which of the following is a sign of heat stress?",
        "answer": 3,
        "source": "OSHA Heat Stress Quick Card (on Tools and Resources CD)",
        "options": [
            "Excessive talking",
            "Excessive giggling",
            "Irritability or confusion",
            "Orange skin under fingernails"
        ]
    },
    {
        "number": 20,
        "tagSid": "4sZixDBCTva",
        "prompt": "Which of the following is a sign of cold stress?",
        "answer": 2,
        "source": "OSHA Cold Stress Quick Card (on Tools and Resources CD)",
        "options": [
            "Fast talking",
            "Loud talking",
            "Dilated pupils",
            "Uncharacteristic comments"
        ]
    }
]